Hello Hello friends welcome to your
own YouTube channel Great Wealth Cattle
I am your friend Atul Goyal today we
will talk again about ICICI Bank, such a bank
which after taking a breakup can give a good feeling by making it
great, we will
talk about where the support zone is,
where should we keep an eye on it, we will
talk about it, first of all let's see the
weekly chart of this bank, it is starting to form, it is at
51.56, that is, and it is a little
low right now, if we go above the coin, there can be a
good bounce in it, if you see this
line, it is working as a good resistance
and this line was working as a support
and also
look at the time, it came around this level, if we took a
printout of it, that topic was formed between these two lines, so
you can take it for
free, but these two lenses are very important,
after that there was a
breakdown here, the stock kept moving between these two lines, it
broke
out against, so that topic like between these two lines  I have been seen
moving, so
look here, this last point, you can
see this line searching,
if its printout is done, then here
we see what is the stand, friends,
as I told you, it is around fifty-one, it is
slightly less, look at the individual minister chart,
friends, you will see it is
around six to two, here the full strength is tees
up, which I want on the yoni side, there is
full strength inside the straight to go up, so
what is being gathered here is
absolutely perfect and here is the stock,
look at this type, as I told you,
right now on the delete, you can clearly see on the fly chart, the
stock is still in a good upward movement,
no problem is visible in it,
look here, there is a chart above the Delhi time frame, this
type will show you, as
we told you, two lines, that the astrologer is working between these two lines, so
look here, a breakout happened above this line,
but it could not stay, its stock
went down quite a bit, then it
went around this registration, then it went down
and  It touches the support line, is
coming up again and touches the support line below.
Now again, a
problem seems to be forming around this resistance line.
If the stock breaks this line, then
this stock
can give a good momentum and go strong. Initially, its
level will be 800 and after that it can
touch this line again at the upper level
which is formed around ₹100. So, it is
important for you to keep these levels in mind. Let's
see this above the two last time frame.
Keep it here at 8 time, so
friends, sometimes it is around 150. And
if you look at this line carefully, then it is
very important to break the levels formed around 748 and move upwards. It is very
important to remove these two labels 748 and 780.
After that, the stock can be seen gaining good momentum. At the
lower level,
like an Ashraf support zone is being formed around 1.5
because there was existence here
earlier.  It has given an out here around 72475, so
now it can act as a good support,
keep a close eye around the seventh force, if the stock
gets here then accommodate it completely,
after this the support relationship which is formed is around
706 to 7 to 8, so if it is
from below you get 725 708, then
you should definitely complete it, now if the stock
breaks these two labels 708 also, then
whenever it will be seen starting again and
reaching here, it will be seen,
you have to keep an eye on the upper level, from the penultimate seven
coat to Shifa John, it is necessary to take it out,
after that it can be seen reaching the level of 800 ₹10
and after that
Jasmine told you that as soon as its resistance
level is broken, then after that
friends, it can catch good momentum, the
aspect will be around 800 ₹10 and
after that the stock will be seen holding this line
which is formed  There are targets around 90,
so definitely complete it,
travel down to 724 hundred and if you press it,
then it
can be seen recovering till here, but this strong support is
not needed, no, don't worry,
you see the trend within it, the
stock is becoming a little flat, oh,
definitely complete it, in the coming time, the
level of notes, that is why the stock can be seen showing,
you will have to have a little patience, you will have to
increase your time holding because there
is a habit of 51.97 for Delhi auto, here
also there is a complete stand,
from any angle this stock is still not visible, the
complete stand is that be it daily chart, weekly
chart or monthly chart and there is a backfoot,
if we take you to the side and if there is a
closing above 155, then definitely the
talk app will be seen gaining momentum, which can take
someone down to the level of nerves,
thank you, thank you.